Maxime Faget Papers
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
- Series VII: Antarctica, 1966-1967
  - Antarctica: Outside, Gilruth Lecture, Aerial View from Plane, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Antarctica: Nussbuam, Lake Bonney, Asgard Range, Victoria Valley Dunes, Cape Royds, Ross Island Slides, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Antarctica: Byrd Station, Long Wire Station, Flying to Pole, Pole Station Slides, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Antarctica: Penguins and McMurdo Base II Slides, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Antarctica: Sampling in the Dry Valley Slides, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Antarctica: Rock Sampling Slides, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Transparencies of Antarctica undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Series VIII: Presentations
  - Transparencies and Presentation Unknown Subject, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2 Transparencies NACA to NASA, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of the First International Symposium on The Technology and Science of Motorless Flight, October 18-21, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Did Teotihuacan's Designers have a Knowledge of Spherical Geometry by Hugh Harleston, Jr., September 15, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - International Academy of Astronautics Reference Forms and Letter, 1984-1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - pace Development Corporation: A Space Consortium, December 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lockheed SPC Spacecraft Development Midterm Briefing, February 14, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SAE Aerospace Vehicle Requirements Conference, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Space Business Roundtable, January-February 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Houston Lyceum Membership Roster, July 11, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Presentation to the National Research Council Committee on the Commercially Developed Space Facility, December 15, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Committee on a Commercially Developed Space Facility, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Wake Shield Facility Flight Program, March 20, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - National Research Council News Report Volume XXXIX Number 5, May 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Presentation Note Cards and Directions, 1990s-? (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - NAL JSC Chapter Board of Directors Meeting Agenda, January 1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Presentation to NASA, September 15, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Statement of Max Faget before Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics Committee on Science U.S. House of Representatives, March 13, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Department of Aerospace Engineering University of Maryland, College Park Glenn L. Martin 50th Anniversary Aerospace Symposium, October 16, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Presentation: Fundamentals of Spacecraft Design undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Addendum, November 16, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Space Operations Center Program Office Presentation, November 1, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Space Operations Purpose Presentation, January 18, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Walt Williams Team Review, April 26, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Walt Williams Team Review - Additional Copy, April 26, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Management Briefing 099 FRF 1 and 2 Hydrogen Detection Data, January-February 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Series IX: Documents Related to Navy Service
  - Steam Table Properties of Saturated and Superheated Steam, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Submarine Related Newspaper Clippings, 1940s (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Navy Photographs, 1940s (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Two Submarine Brochures - Water Damaged?, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Navy and LSU Commencement, 1943; 1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - U. S. Submarine SS 268 Booklet of Central Plans, October 8, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - The Periscope: For the Seventy-Seventh Officers' Class of the School, September 1944 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - SS 414 Submarine Blue Prints, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Submarine Navy Day Program Navy Yard, Mare Island, California, October 27, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Letter from Secretary of Navy James Forrestal June 15,1946, 1946 June 15 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Navy Qualifications Notebook, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Navy Retirement Papers, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Navy Orders, 1943-1960s (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Letter Awarding Certificate from Secretary of Navy, 1961 April 11 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - U. S. Navy Submarine Line-Up, 1964 November 27 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Navy Guide for Retired Personnel and their Families, 1979 February 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Certificate of Retirement - U. S. Navy, 1981 August 26 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Army-Navy Club Application, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Series X: General Biographical Information
  - Miscellaneous Letters to Max Faget, 1970-1990s (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - High School Memorabilia, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Personal Letters to Nancy Faget - s, 1930-1940 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten Book Outline about Gemini and Apollo, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Map and Clipping of Manitowoc, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - NASA's Most Important Asset, by Gerry Griffin, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Sketch of Faget in French, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Birthday Cards to Faget (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Guy Faget Excerpt from The United States Public Health Service, 1798-1950, 1950s (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Symposium on Tropical Medicine The Story of Leprosy in the United States, by Guy Faget, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Thank you letter from Angela Branch to Max Faget, February 16, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Postcard of Farm Unused, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Letters and Poetry, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Poem about Faget, circa 1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Photograph of Faget in Space Suit, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Times-Picayune Front Page, July 18, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Faget's NASA Personnel File, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Thorndike Deland Interview Letter, November 7, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - NASA Biography of Faget, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - NASA Fact Sheet for Faget, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Today's Health Clipping of Let's Remove the Stigma from Leprosy, January 1965 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Letter from Robert Gilruth to L. R. Daniel, JR., January 14, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hall of Fame Congratulations, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Hall of Fame Newspaper Articles, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Background Information and Biographical Details, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - World Leprosy Day February 16, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Letter from James A. Byrd with Money Order, April 15, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - 15 29 London, England Slides, October 1970 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - 15 30 Biographies, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - 15 31 Transcript of Interview with Faget about Skylab by Charles Benson, November 12, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Rough Copy of Autobiographical Sketch for McGraw Hill, August 27, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - The Houston Post NASA Launched 20 Years Ago, October 1, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Investment Letter to Roy Huffington from W. McComb Dunwoody, January 10, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - 18th and 19th Century History of Faget Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - History of Guy Faget, 1925-1950s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Guaranty Federal Savings and Loan, Loan Account Book, 1962-1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Thunderbird Airways Brochures, 1980s (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - NASA Biographical Fact Sheet of Faget, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Retirement News, NASA Release, Daily Citizen, July 29 and 31, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Retirement Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Retirement Letters, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Space News Roundup- Retirement, July 31, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Louisiana State University Football Game, September 1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Faget Retirement Poem, December 1,1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Ore Salvage, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Engineering Week at Goddard, February 1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - James Elms Letters, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Who's Who in Houston, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - The Many Faces of Mignon Faget, October 23, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Letter to E. Henry Grope, December 7, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Social Security Claim Letters (Restricted), 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Personal Letters, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Trip to Belize, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Trip to Belize, February 6, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Space Stories: Oral Histories from the Pioneers of America's Space Program: Faget, November 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Letter Regarding Model Kit of DC - 3, July 22, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Space Stories: Oral Histories from the Pioneers of America's Space Program: Interview #6 Christopher Kraft, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Interview Transcript for Johnson Space Center Oral History Project, August 19, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Photocopy of Robert Grossman Business Card, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Mignon Cressy Faget Obituary, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Mrs. M A Faget Book of the Month Club Solicitation, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - AAA Map of Bellevue and Geometry Formulas, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Drawing of Older Faget with Possible Co -Workers, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Faget (including Vice President George Bush), 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Interview with James Elms, January 13, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Advertisement to Attend Soviet Manned Launch, October 2, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Obituary of James Cornelius Elms with Letter to Nancy and Max Faget from Mrs. James Elms, February 23, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Transcript of NASA Oral History of Faget, June 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Letter from the Allens, Bonnie and Joe, to Faget, February 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Receipt of October 2001 Cruise, August 13, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Max Faget Family Tape Transcripts, December 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Angel Island Interview, September 22, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Transcript of Interview with Faget by John Barry, Steve Clark, Duane Day, Jim Mosquera, June 25, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Letter from William Petynia to Faget with Photographs of Petynia's Boat, May 7, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Online and Newspaper Obituaries of Faget, October 2004 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Obituaries and Mass Pamphlet of Max Faget, October-November, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Marquis Who's Who Publication Board for Herbert Shin Kobayashi, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Slide of Faget, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Faget Biographical Fact Sheet - NASA, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Max Faget Various Resumes, Biographies and Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Resumes of Caldwell Johnson and Joseph Allen, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Vitae with Photographs?, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Faget Biography 1990s with 1978 Photograph (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Space Industries Biography, Age 64, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Resumes and Biographies, Age 65, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Curriculum Vitae of Faget Circa, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Passport Photos of Max and Nancy Faget: Space Industries?, 1990s (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Biography, Age 67, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Series XI: National Academy of Engineering and American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics
  - AIAA/NASA Symposium on the Space Station, July 18-20, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering Bylaws and The Bridge Winter 1984, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Letters from the National Academy of Engineering, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences Report of the Treasurer, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics Papers, 1980s (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering letters and Brochures, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Presentation to the AIAA, April 1, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Engineering Election Forms, 1986-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Engineering Progress Report Fiscal Year 1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics Nomination Forms, 1990-1994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Engineering Election Letter, February 27, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Engineering 1998 Regional Meeting Registrations (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Engineering Ballot for NAE Officer and Councilor Election, March 1, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Engineering Letter and Survey Results, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Series XII: Catalogs, Manuals, and Handbooks
  - Reprint of Hydrogen Peroxide Physical Properties Data Book, December 1954 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Hydrogen Peroxide Handbook, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Thiokol Corporation Space Motor Catalog, circa 1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Space Industries Employee Handbook, September 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Shuttle Thrust Enhancement System: An Unsolicited Proposal; Space Industries, May 11, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Lockheed Launch Vehicles Brochure, Summer 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Series XIII: Advisory Boards and Consulting
  - 1 Grumman Consulting Work, April 26, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - LSU Mechanical Engineering Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Consulting Trips, 1989-1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board Advanced Research and Technology Program, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Tiger Team Meeting with Maps and Travel Itinerary, July 1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - JPL Mesur Meeting August 3-6, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Leap Tiger Team Trip to Los Angeles with Steve Hill, August 3-7, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Consultation with Jet Propulsion Lab, August 5, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Travel to Washington D. C. Hubble Space Telescope Servicing Mission, February 3-4, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - George Washington High School Alumni Association, February 1, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Series XIV: Post-NASA Patents
  - Photocopy of Letter of Patent, November 14, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Invention Disclosure Reentry Thermal Protection and Insulating System for Reusable Cryogenic Stages, January-February-1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Patent Disclosure Letter to Rita Harris from John Holmes Disclosure Document by Max Faget, May 14, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Disclosure Document "Power Pool and Billiard Shooter", December 3, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Disclosure Document for "Additional Solid Rocket Motor for Placement on Space Shuttle External Tanks", November 30, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Invention Disclosure for Side Mounted Mirrors, August 5, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Patent Disclosure Documents for Articulation of Side Mounted Mirrors, August and October 1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Disclosure Document for Powered Pool and Billiard Shooter, November 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Patent Disclosure Dry Recovery of Objects Descending by Parachute, September 14, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Faget about Internal Combustion Cylinder Engine with Patent, July 29, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Series XV: Awards and Honors
  - Fourteenth Annual National Model Airplane Championships, July 1-5, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Flemming Award, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Louisiana State University Press Release, Graduates in Space Program, May 9, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Space Hall of Fame Dinner - Photographs, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Clippings and Programs for LSU Honors Day, May 1962 23 6 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Honors Award Program, October 25, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Banquet of the Golden Plate, December 1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Academy of Achievement Golden Plate Award Brochure, December 29, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Sword of Loyola Award Dinner, Invitation, Program, and Ephemera, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Flemming Award Clippings, April 3, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - American Astronautical Society Award Letter, March 22, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Insulation Conference, Golden Omega Award, October 18, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - NASA Honors Awards Ceremony, October 24, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Letter of Election to the American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, August 16, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - NASA Exceptional Service Medal/Special Honor Awards Ceremony, January 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Space Hall of Fame Announcement, August 24, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National Space Hall of Fame Awards Dinner, September 26, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Awards Certificates 1970s, July 26, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sailing with Championship Chevrons, July 26, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Roundup Faget Presents Service Awards, January 16, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Engineering 1970 Election (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - AIAA President's Reception and Honors Banquet, Spacecraft Design Award, October 22, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Various Awards, 1933-1970s (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - LSU Alumnus of the Year Award, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Program and Newspaper Clippings LSU, May 27, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous LSU with Photograph and Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Citation for Honorary Degree of Doctor of Engineering, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Daniel and Florence Guggenheim International Astronautics Award August-September 1973, August-09-1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers Annual Honors and Awards Program, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Roster 1976 ISA Honors and Awards (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - 1976 Albert F. Sperry Medal Award Brochure (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - 1976 Harry Diamond Award Nomination and Award Letter, September 30, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Harry Diamond Memorial Award, May 20, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Newsletter LSU Announcing American Society of Mechanical Engineering Gold Medal, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Houston Independent School District Distinguished Leadership Award, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Rank Awards for Senior Executive Service, September 9, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Presidential Luncheon STS - 1, May 19, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Rice University Seminar, November 19-20, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Letter of Congratulations from Jimmy Carter, November 23, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - L -5 Society Talk, March 1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics 50th Anniversary Celebration Houston Section, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Houston Patent Law Association Award, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Space Shuttle Program Technical Conference, June 28-30, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Spacesystems Award, May 20, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - ASME George Westinghouse Gold Medal Nomination Form, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - 1984 I. B. Laskowitz Award for Research in Aerospace Engineering Sciences, Support Systems, and Components, December 12, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Rotary National Award for Space Achievement with Letter of Acceptance to Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - National Rotary Award for Space Achievement Brochure and Photograph, March 12, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Rotary Award Clipping, March 12, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Gala Dinner to Honor Astronauts October 1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - American Astronautical Society Honors Night Banquet, November 4, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Jack Swigert Memorial Ball, April 9, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Receipt from NASA Invention Award Check for "Space Shuttle Vehicle and System", undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Various Certificates of Recognition, 1940s-1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - LSU Certificate of Recognition and Case, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - United States Olympic Society, August 1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Nomination of Robert Gilruth for the Charles Stark Draper Prize, February 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Space Hall of Fame Induction, September 1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Photograph of Rotary Dinner, March 25, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - AIAA 1991 Honors Night Banquet Program, May 2, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Engineering Hall of Distinction Louisiana State University, November 20, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Award Nomination Forms, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Rotary National Award for Space Achievement Brochures, 1988-1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Charles Hartman, President Rotary National Award for Space Achievement, February 1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Faget Letter of Appreciation from NASA, November 5, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Photo Negatives of Award Presentation with Note from Helen Harris, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Induction into the National Inventors Hall of Fame, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - National Award for Space Achievement, September 2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Laureate Awards and Laureates Hall of Fame Program, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Certificate of MPAD Naturalization - Mission Planning and Analysis Division, July 20, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Series XVI: Publications and Technical Reports
  - Letter Regarding Space Station Prototype Water Electrolysis Vendor Selection, January 31, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Kistler Aerospace K-1 Vehicle Program Review, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Various Papers on Ablation Characteristics of Ceramic, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Computer Generated Test Data, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Kistler Research, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Systems Research Incorporated Qualifications Summary, 1994? (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Comparative Performance Estimations for Shuttle Standard Orbiter Using RSRM's, June 7, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Two Stage Balloon Assisted Launch-Vehicle, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Technical Analysis Data Mars Mission Payload and Flyback F-1 Launching Two Castor 120s, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Balloon Assisted Launch Vehicle, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Basic Kistler, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Kistler, February 21, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - LRB Recovery and Flyback to Launch Site, April 16, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Technical Analysis of Fly Back F- 1 Launching Two Castor 120s and a Single Castor 120 Upper Stages, July 24, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Super Kistler Analysis, September 1996 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Scope - IEEE Volume 21 Number 7, March 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Engineering and Development Directorate 1977 and Test Highlights May 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - LSU Engineering Newsletter, Fall 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Engineering and Development Directorate 1979 and Test Highlights July 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Circuit Path Option, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Manned Orbit Transfer Vehicles and their Missions, September 6-12, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Satellite Servicing from the Shuttle Orbiter by Richard Kline and Rudolph Adornato, September 6-12, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - AN Overview of United States Manned Space Flight from Mercury to the Shuttle, September 6-12, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Space Technology Innovation Max Faget: Space Program Management. Then and Now, May/June 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Air and Space Magazine: National Air and Space Museum Smithsonian Institution Volume 6 Number 2 Project Mercury Article, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Various Working Documents with Handwritten Notes 332-7505, 1991? (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Florida Trend Who Killed the American Space Program, February 1992 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Boat Tail Orbiter Powered Abort, April and December 1992 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Tequila - A Four Stage Vehicle Using H-1800, Castor IV-B, or Bus and Star 48-B, December 22, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Space Technology Innovation, May/June 1993 (Box 28, Folder 15)